{
    "quiz" : [
        {
            "category" : "Easy",
            "question" : "How much food do each singaporeans waste everyday?",
            "options" : [
                "1.4 billion kg",
                "2 bowls of rice",
                "10kg of rice",
                "744 million kg"
            ],
            "correctIndex" : 1
        },
        {
            "category" : "Easy",
            "question" : "What are the 3 Rs of sustainbility?",
            "options" : [
                "reduce, rebuild, regain",
                "reuse, reduce, regain",
                "reduce, reuse, recycle",
                "rebuild, recycle, rebuild"
            ],
            "correctIndex" : 2
        },
        {
            "category" : "Easy",
            "question" : "how long does it take for honey to expire?",
            "options" : [
                "6 months",
                "1 year",
                "10 years",
                "never"
            ],
            "correctIndex" : 3
        },
        {
            "category" : "Easy",
            "question" : "what does NEA stand for?",
            "options" : [
                " National Environment Agency ",
                "North East Association",
                "Natural Enironment Adaptation ",
                "Nature Earth Association"
            ],
            "correctIndex" : 0
        },
        {
            "category" : "Easy",
            "question" : "what are the 3 most important elements of our life?",
            "options" : [
                "air shelter food",
                "air water shelter",
                "food clothes water",
                "air water food"
            ],
            "correctIndex" : 3
        },
        {
            "category" : "Easy",
            "question" : "Which of the following is false about food sustainability?",
            "options" : [
                "Choose organic and local foods that are in season",
                "Reduce your food waste by planning meals ahead of time",
                "Compost your food waste when possible ",
                "Consume food that are high on the food chain"
            ],
            "correctIndex" : 3
        },
        
        {
            "category" : "Medium",
            "question" : "Local grown tomatoes do less harm to the environment compared to imported tomatoes",
            "options" : [
                "True",
                "False",
                "",
                ""
            ],
            "correctIndex" : 0
        },
        {
            "category" : "Medium",
            "question" : "How much of the worldâ€™s food is never eaten and thrown away? ",
            "options" : [
                "10%",
                "15%",
                "20%",
                "25%"
            ],
            "correctIndex" : 3
        },
        {
            "category" : "Medium",
            "question" : "How much water does it take to make a cup of coffee(125ml)",
            "options" : [
                "130 ml",
                "1.3 L",
                "13 L",
                "130 L"
            ],
            "correctIndex" : 3
        },
         {
            "category" : "Medium",
            "question" : "Of the estimated 1 billion tons of food that goes to waste every year, much of it is perfectly edible and nutritious?",
            "options" : [
                "True",
                "False",
                "",
                ""
            ],
            "correctIndex" : 0
        },
        {
            "category" : "Medium",
            "question" : "Upcycled food is all about elevating food to its...",
            "options" : [
                "Least expensive use",
                "Most expensive use",
                "Highest % Best use",
                "Most popular use"
            ],
            "correctIndex" : 2
        },
        {
            "category" : "Hard",
            "question" : "which of the following home products cannot be used as fertilizers?",
            "options" : [
                "coffee grounds",
                "banana peels",
                "chicken skin",
                "egg shells"
            ],
            "correctIndex" : 0
        },
                {
            "category" : "hard",
            "question" : "which of the following is not a food donation drive in singapore?",
            "options" : [
                "daily bread food bank",
                "the food bank singapore",
                "free food for all",
                "the food pantry"
            ],
            "correctIndex" : 0
        },
         {
            "category" : "hard",
            "question" : "Which food types produces the least carbon foodprint?",
            "options" : [
                "dairy produce",
                "fruits & vegetables",
                "nuts & legume",
                "oil"
            ],
            "correctIndex" : 2
        },
        {
            "category" : "hard",
            "question" : "How much  greenhouse gas emission, in terms of Kg, does it take to produce one kg of beef?",
            "options" : [
                "3kg",
                "6kg",
                "60kg",
                "30kg"
            ],
            "correctIndex" : 2
        },
    ]
}

 
